Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Financial
  - Royalties - D-J, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Royalties - K-Q, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Royalties - R-Z, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Royalties - A-K, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Royalties - L-Z, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Royalties - A-B, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Royalties - C-D, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Royalties - E-G, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Royalties - H-L, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Royalties - M-Q, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Royalties - R-T, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 2-3)
  - Royalties - U-Z, 1996-1997 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Royalties, 1996-1999 (Box 68, Folder 5-12)
  - Royalties for "Lost Authors", 1983-1995 (Box 68, Folder 13-16)